{
  "decks": [
    {
      "name": "Rendering in React",
      "description": "React's component structure allows for quickly building a complex web application that relies on DOM manipulation.",
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "name": "React Router",
      "description": "React Router is a collection of navigational components that compose declaratively with your application.",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "Test at 6:50 p.m.",
      "description": "Test at 6:50 p.m.",
      "id": 4
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "GoodBye",
      "back": "Good-Bye Again 2asdfg",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "How do you modify the state of a different React component?",
      "back": "Not at all! State is visible to the component only.",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "front": "What does <Switch> do?",
      "back": "Renders the first matching child <Route> ",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "front": "Test Front",
      "back": "Test Back",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "front": "I just added this at 3:33 p.m.",
      "back": "This is back of the just added at 3:33 p.m.",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "front": "Hello",
      "back": "Good-Bye",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "front": "This is front of card 1",
      "back": "This is back of card 1werfee3rfgs",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "front": "This if front of card 2",
      "back": "This if back of card 2",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 13
    },
    {
      "front": "This if front of card 3",
      "back": "This if back of card 3",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "front": "This is front of card 4",
      "back": "This if back of card 42dee",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 15
    },
    {
      "front": "w23erf",
      "back": "2we3r4fgerfgt3e4rfss helloo",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 16
    },
    {
      "front": "pizza",
      "back": "pizza33",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 17
    },
    {
      "front": "1234ergt",
      "back": "2we3r4gt",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 18
    },
    {
      "front": "e34rthyju7y65",
      "back": "23er4gt",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 19
    }
  ]
}